<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Brenton Salmi</title>
    <description>Brents Personal Website</description>
    <link>http://www.brentonsalmi.com/</link>
    <atom:link href="http://www.brentonsalmi.com/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <pubDate>Sun, 01 Nov 2020 22:24:46 -0800</pubDate>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 01 Nov 2020 22:24:46 -0800</lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Jekyll v3.8.5</generator>
    
      <item>
        <title>SOTA Activation W6/SC-213</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;In late October 2020 Mack and I were supposed to start a 3 day bike-packing trip into the Portola Redwoods but this turned into a 2 day adventure in the &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.nps.gov/pinn/index.htm&quot;&gt;Pinnacles National Park&lt;/a&gt;! A last minute Red-Flag warning and 40-50MPH wind gusts in Portola made our expected stay under the Redwoods a bit unnerving! We instead decided to head to the Pinnacles hiking, climbing, and I even brought my new Elecraft KX2 amateur radio to attempt a SOTA activation of &lt;a href=&quot;https://summits.sota.org.uk/summit/W6/SC-213&quot;&gt;W6/SC-213 Hawkins Peak&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/2020_10_30/DSC06925.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Brenton Salmi, KB1LQD, operating his KX2 radio during a SOTA activation of Hawkins Peak in the Pinnacles National Park.&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;activating-hawkins-peak-w6sc-213&quot;&gt;Activating Hawkins Peak W6/SC-213&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Mack and I set off along the familiar path of the Condor Gulch trail, one we’ve been down several times to hike to climbing spots such as &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.mountainproject.com/area/105807251/the-sisters&quot;&gt;The Sisters&lt;/a&gt; or &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.mountainproject.com/area/107173454/teaching-rock&quot;&gt;Teaching Rock&lt;/a&gt; in prior trips. This time we stuck right climb up the Condor Gulch Trail leading to Hawkins peak (via the High Peaks Trail). We had left from the Bay Area later in the day and the sun was bearing down at the start of our hike but it slowly let up over the miles we gained, a gentle breeze even welcomed us to the summit! The summit trail is actually a small “climbers trail” along the High Peaks Trail that brings you through a small jumble of boulders and bushes before you find yourself in the unique Hawkins Peak meadow. There is no technical climbing or exposure required to get to this spot, at most a small section of class 3 scramble up a rock incline is the most you’ll encounter on this small trail.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/2020_10_30/SOTA_LOCATION_GPS_FAR.png&quot; alt=&quot;Google Earth view of our route from the East side of the Pinnacles National Park.&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;When we arrived at the meadow we immediately knew this was going to be a great spot for a late lunch with many spires providing shade (except for those arriving at noon). Checking my SOTA iPhone app confirmed we were in the activation zone! Do note that this is also an active area for climbers along the small spires and large cliffs. You’ll likely be alone but if people are climbing stay clear of setting up beneath them on any side of a spire they are climbing. The is AMPLE room in the activation zone for spots and antennas. Pinnacles is known for less than stellar rock quality and even previously solid rocks within the formations can come loose and fall, especially when being climbed. The approximate spot we operated from is &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.google.com/maps/place/36%C2%B029'17.9%22N+121%C2%B011'50.8%22W/@36.4881076,-121.1975877,202m/data=!3m1!1e3!4m5!3m4!1s0x0:0x0!8m2!3d36.4883014!4d-121.1974345!5m1!1e4&quot;&gt;36.48830139,-121.19743446&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/2020_10_30/SOTA_LOCATION_GPS_CLOSE.png&quot; alt=&quot;A close up Google Earth view of Hawkins Peak Pinnacles National Park.&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I brought along my new &lt;a href=&quot;https://elecraft.com/products/kx2-ssb-cw-data-80-10-m-transceiver&quot;&gt;Elecraft KX2&lt;/a&gt; and a home built end-fed “random” 85 foot wire with a sufficient counterpoise fed by a home built 9:1 unun (unbalanced-to-unbalanced auto-transformer). I created a small common mode choke using the coax at the unun and mix 43 ferrite I had on hand to avoid any RF on the coax shield. Occasionally I’ve found the CW keys of the KX2 get a bit “hot” with RF in the right conditions without it. We didn’t have a mast with us and instead relied on the rocks and trees to lay the wires a few feet off the ground. This was the first time using both this radio and this antenna. In SOTA setups you try to avoid the ground losses you can but it’s a diminishing returns battle and your fighting sunlight and cold winds at the same time! We’re already on a mountain peak, let’s call it good.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/2020_10_30/DSC06936.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;A photo of our antenna setup.&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/2020_10_30/DSC06919.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Brenton Salmi, KB1LQD, operating his KX2 radio during a SOTA activation of Hawkins Peak in the Pinnacles National Park.&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We fired up 20 meters first (14 MHz amateur band) and attempted to respond to CW (Morse Code) and SSB (Single Side Band - Voice) stations and call CQ ourselves. The band was not working and we didn’t have a prior SOTA reflector spot enabled so our only option was calling CQ SOTA. I brought up 85 feet of 22AWG wire so I could work the lower bands and that is exactly what we did! It was nearing 5PM PDT so the lower bands were going to be a good bet. I auto-tuned to 40 meters (7MHz amateur band) and noticed the much better activity (it still amazes me how much LESS RF noise rural areas have compared to the the San Francisco Bay area)! Holding my phone (Verizon) in the right spot gave us a burst of reception and we took this opportunity to (SOTA) spot ourselves on 40 meters SSB. Almost immediately the stations came in, Hawkins peak last saw an activation nearly 3 years prior in 2017! California, Oregon, Washington… our 10W of power was reaching out with an average SSB RST (Readability, Signal, Tone) report of 45 to 55 along the west coast and out to Texas. After working a number of stations I moved to the CW band and reached out to the East Coast (Kentucky)!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;After 13 contacts it was getting cold and dark and we had a few miles of downhill hiking ahead of us, food, and camp, so we called it a night.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;climbing-the-flatiron&quot;&gt;Climbing The Flatiron&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The next morning we set off again, this time our radios replaced by harnesses, rope, carabiners, and other assorted rock climbing equipment (we did bring my Yeasu VX-8R but had no luck on 146.52 MHz calling out during the day). This gear was much heavier than my KX2, unfortunately. We set off to find the Flatiron rock climbing area to try some easier 5.0 and 5.3 sport climbs. “Sport” is a relative term in Pinnacles where bolts can be spaced out 10-20 feet apart on the suspect Pinnacles rock quality. It’s prudent to keep an eye out for rocks, horns, or other natural features to sling as added protection. Neither Mack or I had climbed, at all, in many months (this is the Covid-19 era…) so we were taking it easy. The first route, unprotected 5.0 climbing to the first bolt around a rock out-cropping was too much for my risk assessment and I down-climbed.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I jumped over to the 5.3 route nearby and climbed up to a ledge where the 3rd bolt of the route was. This looked much easier and less sketchy from the ground! Reaching the next bolt required traversing 10 feet across the ledge and climbing up and over another 5 feet. Falling here would be bad, hitting the ledge(s) and scrapping a very long way down. The lonely little shrub pointed out by the guide book on this ledge was about the size of my thumb, less that stellar for trusting with my health and safety. This is the first time I have ever bailed from a route and left gear behind. Scouting for additional natural protection but coming up empty handed I decided to play it safe and come down. I cut off a few feet of webbing, grabbed a rappel ring from my harness, and fashioned a water knot to the 3rd bolt and got lowered. It happens, it was a good lesson considering I’ve climbing harder routes in the Pinnacles with just as long run-out bolts.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/2020_10_30/DSC07029-1.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Brenton Salmi, KB1LQD, studying climbing routes.&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;climbing-bynums-spire-hawkins-peak&quot;&gt;Climbing Bynum’s Spire (Hawkins Peak!)&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Having bailed from the Flatiron we settled for a nice long hike along the high peaks trail. This trail has multiple narrow and steep sections, I imagine some people do get hurt here just hiking each year. We decided to checkout out the Hawkins Peak area for smaller climbs, we’d just been here the day prior activating the same spot for SOTA! Bynum’s Spire is the rock I leaned back on operating my amateur radio, I thought this was pretty cool :)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/2020_10_30/IMG_3181.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Brenton Salmi, KB1LQD, at the top of Bynum's Spire.&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This route is only a 5.2 but the first, and only, bolt is about 20 feet high, it’s a bit sporty (and mossy). I did some investigation with my camera’s zoom lens and hopping on nearby boulders to verify the route actually has an anchor at the top. The guide book doesn’t show one and the &lt;a href=&quot;http://bayareaclimbing.blogspot.com/2011/09/pinnacles-national-monument.html&quot;&gt;“Pinnacles Rappel”&lt;/a&gt; (simul-rapelling off two sides of a pinnacle) is a real thing I don’t really want to do.  I set up a quick top-rope while the Condors flew around the nearby spires (there were no active Condor closures that I could find for the area, always check!).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/2020_10_30/IMG_3184.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Brenton Salmi's shadow from Bynum's Spire cast onto Tuff Dome'.&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/2020_10_30/IMG_3185.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;A quick quad top-rope anchor setup.&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We got a lap or two on the rock and the sun was setting. It was time to get our headlamps out, grab a snack, and head back home.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/2020_10_30/DSC07051.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Mack coiling the rope after climbing.&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We continued back down the Condor Gulch trail we’d taken the day prior. It was complete darkness when we ran into another group going much slower than us when we realized this was actually the San Benito Search and Rescue team carrying out an injured person. We gave them a good 100 or so feet distance, there was no point to passing and making them worry about us. We eventually passed when they let us go by taking a break at a switchback but we cut the trail a bit to give them distance. I didn’t see climbing gear but we’re not sure what happened, we were near the high peaks trail with many dangerous hiking cliff staircases… It didn’t appear life threatening thankfully and I hope they are safe and recovering! Experiences like this, especially having bailed from a route hours earlier for my own safety is a good reminder of how fragile and quick to unravel outdoor adventures can become.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Having turned our 3 day vacation into 2 days in the Pinnacles getting some great hiking, climbing, and even a SOTA amateur radio activation in we were happy, albeit a bit tired. There are several other SOTA peaks in the Pinnacles and I’m sure we’ll return to activate the others among our climbing and hiking adventures here. Pinnacles holds a bit of a hesitant love in my heart - hot, run-out climbs, but always adventures.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;sota-lessons-learned&quot;&gt;SOTA Lessons Learned&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Here are a few lessons learned activating the SOTA summit.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;A mast would allow for quicker and better antenna setups
    &lt;ul&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;A bit more height  to reduce transmit ground losses (but height isn’t too critical if you’re on a summit)&lt;/li&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;Not reliant on height/distant to trees or boulders&lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;/ul&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;climbing-lessons-learned&quot;&gt;Climbing Lessons Learned&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Here are a few lessons learned from climbing during this trip.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;COVID-19 has stopped our climbing gym training and this greatly affects:
    &lt;ul&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;Physical ability - Especially the climbing specific toe/fingers&lt;/li&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;Mental ability - Everything is a bit scarier&lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;/ul&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Bailing is OK - This is a dangerous activity and trust your gut.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Sun, 25 Oct 2020 17:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
        <link>http://www.brentonsalmi.com/2020/pinnaclesnps-sota-hawkins-peak/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.brentonsalmi.com/2020/pinnaclesnps-sota-hawkins-peak/</guid>
        
        <category>ham radio</category>
        
        <category>sota</category>
        
        <category>climbing</category>
        
        <category>radio</category>
        
        
        <category>amateur radio</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Climbing Mount Shasta Via West Face Route 2019</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;During the weekend of July 13th, 2019 my climbing partner and I attempted and succeeded in climbing &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.shastaavalanche.org/general-route-description/west-face&quot;&gt;Mt. Shasta via the West Face&lt;/a&gt;. This was my first large mountaineering climb without a guide and having planned the trip ourselves. A cold alpine start ran into mild altitude sickness, navigation error, and unexpected weather on our descent. This is a (very late) trip report detailing our planning, the climb, and lessons learned.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h1 id=&quot;the-plan&quot;&gt;The Plan&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Our plan was to drive to Mt. Shasta during the early day and hike during the afternoon from the Bunny Flats trailhead to the Hidden Valley camp Saturday to set up camp. We’d then get an alpine start on the summit bid at 2am on Sunday morning continuing up the standard West Face route that links to Misery Hill for the final summit climb. Our absolute turn around time was set for noon.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h1 id=&quot;the-climb&quot;&gt;The Climb&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;p&gt;My partner and I set off from the Bay area for a 6 hour drive to Bunny Flat trailhead parking. It was an exciting start albeit felt a bit awkward leaving for a mountain so late in the morning but this worked out quite well! The trek was mostly wet dirt except for scattered patches of snow up to the &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.sierraclubfoundation.org/what-we-fund/horse-camp-mt-shasta&quot;&gt;Horse Camp hut&lt;/a&gt;. The trail to Hidden Valley camp threw a few scree fields and isolated snowfields to traverse. We arrived at camp a few hours before sunset and had just enough time to cook and prepare for the next morning without roasting on the mountain during the daytime in our tent.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/climbing/shasta_2019_medium/DSC03779.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;The view looking down from the Mt. Shasta trail leading to Hidden Valley camp.&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Hidden Valley campsites were on dry ground surrounded by the snowfield in front of the West Face. We met only a handful of other climbers on this route, I actually knew and worked with a few of them in my past life at SpaceX… It’s a small world! As my partner made his way to bed I took a half hour or so to take some night photography shots of Mt. Shasta. It was a beautiful, seemingly full moon lit night that blew wispy clouds sporadically off the peak. Our mission the next day was to safely climb up the middle of this photo below.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/climbing/shasta_2019_medium/DSC03844.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;A moonlit night photo of the Mt. Shasta West Face.&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Before settling in for bed we discussed and decided to move our wake-up time to 1:30am. Alarms buzzed and we woke, made coffee, ate, and dressed for the adventure awaiting us. Hiking across the snow and rock field to the first real incline was much longer than it seemed during the daytime. We were greeted with a steep incline within a chute that lead to a more reasonable sustained climb up the brunt of the face. We made good time and felt great (and of course a bit tired from our alpine start) as the sun began to rise.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/climbing/shasta_2019_medium/DSC03888.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Looking down at my partner climbing the West Face route of Mt. Shasta.&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As we trudged onward we could hear the excitement in our voices turn to a mixture of tired, heavy breathing at the high altitude. We had several thousand feet of climbing to do and thick clouds rolled in partially causing a navigation error on my part leading us a bit off route to the climbers right. We fixed the error when we realized and continued upwards.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/climbing/shasta_2019_medium/DSC03912.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;A view of the steep snowfield climb of the Mt. Shasta West Face nearing the top of the route.&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;My partner was starting to feel mild &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.altitude.org/altitude-sickness&quot;&gt;altitude sickness&lt;/a&gt;. I knew that in the past I’ve felt it above 12,000 feet and was assessing myself, and my partner. Surprisingly, I was feeling great. We decided to continue at a slower pace and make sure we’re eating and drinking. I began to watch him more closely and ensure his altitude sickness was the “I’m feeling nauseous and tired” kind and didn’t start showing signs of incoherence, wobbling, or threatening to vomit. We made way up for the top of the West Face route that meets with the Avalanche Gulch (and several other routes) at Misery Hill.
The last few hundred feet of elevation had some of the steepest snow on the route. I was a bit nervous prior but being on this ~40 degree slope but it felt much more comfortable in person! Reaching the ~13,000 foot West Face We agreed that if I felt he was progressing towards more severe symptoms we’d turn around no questions asked on his part. He also could turn us around with no questions asked.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/climbing/shasta_2019_medium/DSC03916.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;My climbing partner taking a rest at the top of the Mt. Shasta West Face route.&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;At the top of the West Face the view was beautiful! We could gaze down into the Whitney Glacier and then over to Misery Hill. Misery Hill was dotted with specs of climbers slowly making their way up the aptly named hill. The West Face provides a comforting false summit leaving all of Misery Hill’s not so comforting ~1000 feet of elevation for round two. We traversed above the Whitney Glacier and found ourselves amongst the crowds of Avalanche Gulch climbing our last hill.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/climbing/shasta_2019_medium/DSC04017.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Looking back along the Whitney Glacier towards the West Face route while at Misery Hill (Mt. Shasta).&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/climbing/shasta_2019_medium/DSC03972.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;A selfie climbing the last spire of Mt. Shasta to the summit.&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Misery Hill was mostly a rocky trail this late in the season, my partner was still feeling the altitude and slow but in good spirits! Lightly spotted clouds formed around us and brought the occasional snowflakes passing by us. This made for an amazing summit climb but may have been a forewarning to our descent…&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/climbing/shasta_2019_medium/DSC03940.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;My climbing parter on Misery Hill (Mt. Shasta).&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We reached the summit at approximately 11am and signed the summit log, took some photos, and took in the view. Now we were tired and no longer had the summit ahead of us but instead 5,000 feet of descending to our camp then packing out to our car.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/climbing/shasta_2019_medium/DSC03993.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;My climbing partner and I on the summit of Mt. Shasta July 2019.&quot; /&gt; 
&lt;img src=&quot;/images/climbing/shasta_2019_medium/DSC03997.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;My climbing partner and I signed summit logged book.&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As we traversed above the Whitney Glacier thicker clouds rolled in, some being thick enough to risk not seeing eachother 50 feet apart! We stayed close and found the top of the West Face route again. The other climbing party on the west face had already descended and we found their glissading tracks. We happily knew this route let climbers glissade nearly the entire ~4,000 feet and took our opportunity. I’d never glissaded THAT MUCH before, it was an amazing experience with the benefit of letting us descend to the camp plateau in just over 20 minutes!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/climbing/shasta_2019_medium/DSC04010.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;A photo of my climbing partner as thick clouds rolled in at the base of Misery Hill (Mt. Shasta).&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As we walked the flat portion of Hidden Valley camp’s snowfield, over a lot of &lt;a href=&quot;https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Watermelon_snow&quot;&gt;watermelon snow&lt;/a&gt;, we heard the first thunder in the distance. We were still well above any tree cover. Anxiously we packed and quickly made our way to Horse Camp where we had tree cover. Tree cover is not ideal… but I’ll take ground voltage differentials over a direct hit anyday. We got rained on, scared, but made it to the car for a very, very, very tired drive home.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h1 id=&quot;the-lessons-learned&quot;&gt;The Lessons Learned&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Lacking cardio fitness likely exaggerated my climbing partner’s his altitude sickness&lt;/strong&gt;
    &lt;ul&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;Altitude sickness can be hard to gauge with summit fever pulling and the vagueness of severity.&lt;/li&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;We were actually making risky call to continue going up&lt;/li&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;Climb with people who you trust WILL turn themselves around (and do them that favor yourself as well)&lt;/li&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;Arriving to camp so late left little time for acclimatization&lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;/ul&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Get as much rest as possible with an alpine start&lt;/strong&gt;
    &lt;ul&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;A likely contibutor to the altitude sickness was our lack of sleep (few hours at most)&lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;/ul&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Be weary of in-field navigation changes, question why you think that is the right thing to do&lt;/strong&gt;
    &lt;ul&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;Rock bands in clouds are hard to navigate, they all look the same up close&lt;/li&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;We started climbing towards a chute linking Casaval ridge before realizing this was not correct and certainly not easier to climb.&lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;/ul&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Weather happens quick, without forecast warning, trust your gut when clouds tell you something is brewing&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Tue, 25 Feb 2020 16:00:00 -0800</pubDate>
        <link>http://www.brentonsalmi.com/2020/climbing-mt-shasta-2019/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.brentonsalmi.com/2020/climbing-mt-shasta-2019/</guid>
        
        <category>mountaineering</category>
        
        <category>mt. shasta</category>
        
        <category>west face route</category>
        
        <category>california</category>
        
        <category>night photography</category>
        
        <category>mountains</category>
        
        
        <category>mountaineering</category>
        
        <category>adventure</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>New Website!</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;It’s been a good start to 2020 and now I’m finally bringing up a new website base on &lt;a href=&quot;https://jekyllrb.com/&quot;&gt;Jekyll&lt;/a&gt;! I intend to showcase my photography, projects, and adventures in a very loose informal way.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I’ll slowly be adding to this website by updating both content and layout.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/2020-02-18/DSC01991.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Climbing Waterfall Cliffs - Castle Rock State Park&quot; height=&quot;512px&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 17 Feb 2020 16:34:00 -0800</pubDate>
        <link>http://www.brentonsalmi.com/2020/new-website/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.brentonsalmi.com/2020/new-website/</guid>
        
        <category>website</category>
        
        
        <category>website</category>
        
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
